<Items>
  <Item ItemID="1043374545">
    <Name>christopher radko | fritz n_ frosty sledding</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Christopher Radko</Category>
    <Currently>$30.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$30.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids />
    <Location>its a dry heat</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-03-01 18:10:40</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-13-01 18:10:40</Ends>
    <Seller Rating="1035" UserID="rulabula" />
    <Description>brand new beautiful handmade european blown glass ornament from christopher radko. this particular ornament features a snowman paired with a little girl bundled up in here pale blue coat sledding along on a silver and blue sled filled with packages. the ornament is approximately 5_ tall and 4_ wide. brand new and never displayed, it is in its clear plastic packaging and comes in the signature black radko gift box. PLEASE READ CAREFULLY!!!! payment by cashier's check, money order, or personal check. personal checks must clear before shipping. the hold period will be a minimum of 14 days. I ship with UPS and the buyer is responsible for shipping charges. the shipping rate is dependent on both the weight of the package and the distance that package will travel. the minimum shipping/handling charge is $6 and will increase with distance and weight. shipment will occur within 2 to 5 days after the deposit of funds. a $2 surcharge will apply for all USPS shipments if you cannot have or do not want ups service. If you are in need of rush shipping, please let me know and I_will furnish quotes on availability. the BUY-IT-NOW price includes free domestic shipping (international winners and residents of alaska and hawaii receive a credit of like value applied towards their total) and, as an added convenience, you can pay with paypal if you utilize the feature. paypal is not accepted if you win the auction during the course of the regular bidding-I only accept paypal if the buy it now feature is utilized. thank you for your understanding and good luck! Free Honesty Counters powered by Andale! Payment Details See item description and Payment Instructions, or contact seller for more information. Payment Instructions See item description or contact seller for more information.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1043397459">
    <Name>PM BOY AND GIRL EXCLUSIVE EVENT PIECE LE</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Enesco</Category>
    <Category>Precious Moments</Category>
    <Currently>$99.99</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$99.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids />
    <Location Latitude="41.901849" Longitude="-75.10493">LONG ISLAND USA</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-03-01 18:38:23</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-13-01 18:38:23</Ends>
    <Seller Rating="221" UserID="dollface94" />
    <Description>YOU ARE ALWAYS IN MY HEART IS THE NAME OF IT ,HAS A BOY AND A GIRL EACH SITTING IN A HEART SHAPED SHELL ON A BENCH THESE PIECES ARE RARE AND EXCLUSIVE YOU GET BOTH PIECES IN YOUR BID THEY ARE MINT NEVER BEEN DISPLAYED BRAND NEW IN BOXES .... ALSO TAKE PAYPALBUYER PAYS 8.00 SHIPPING</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1043402767">
    <Name>Precious Moments Girl Stove Mini Tea Set</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Enesco</Category>
    <Category>Precious Moments</Category>
    <Currently>$4.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$4.00</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>1</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder Rating="2919" UserID="goldcoastvideo">
          <Location>Los Angeles,CA</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-06-01 06:44:54</Time>
        <Amount>$4.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location Latitude="43.017412" Longitude="-87.569664">MIlwaukee Wi</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-03-01 18:44:54</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-13-01 18:44:54</Ends>
    <Seller Rating="952" UserID="fallsantiques" />
    <Description>PRECIOUS MOMENTS GIRL/STOVE MINI TEA SET: This really cute little mini decorative teaset is mint in box. It was only removed for photo. It is about 6 inches across. Original price was $20.00. Buyer to pay postage and handling of $4.50 for delivery in USA.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1043402785">
    <Name>Beatrix Potter Tailor of Gloucester Shakers</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Enesco</Category>
    <Category>Other Enesco Items</Category>
    <Currently>$3.50</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$3.50</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>0</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids />
    <Location Latitude="43.017412" Longitude="-87.569664">MIlwaukee Wi</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-03-01 18:44:55</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-13-01 18:44:55</Ends>
    <Seller Rating="952" UserID="fallsantiques" />
    <Description>BEATRIX POTTER TAILOR OF GLOUSCESTER SHAKERS: Really cute set of figural salt and pepper shakers of the mouse tailor and two spools of thread. It is mint in box. Original price was $15.00. Buyer to pay postage and handling of $4.50 for delivery in USA.</Description>
  </Item>
  <Item ItemID="1043495702">
    <Name>Precious Moments Fig-ANGEL OF MERCY- NURSE</Name>
    <Category>Collectibles</Category>
    <Category>Decorative &amp; Holiday</Category>
    <Category>Decorative by Brand</Category>
    <Category>Enesco</Category>
    <Category>Precious Moments</Category>
    <Currently>$28.00</Currently>
    <First_Bid>$9.99</First_Bid>
    <Number_of_Bids>6</Number_of_Bids>
    <Bids>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder Rating="427" UserID="nobody138">
          <Location>GOD BLESS AMERICA, FROM SOUTH, MS</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-04-01 23:20:07</Time>
        <Amount>$12.99</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder Rating="1" UserID="danielhb2000">
          <Location>Huntington Beach, Ca.</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-06-01 02:00:07</Time>
        <Amount>$15.99</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder Rating="106" UserID="boncon123">
          <Location>Northern Ireland</Location>
          <Country>United Kingdom</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-07-01 04:40:07</Time>
        <Amount>$18.99</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder Rating="37" UserID="watchdenmark">
          <Location>Munich</Location>
          <Country>Germany</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-08-01 07:20:07</Time>
        <Amount>$22.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder Rating="92" UserID="mrwvh">
          <Location>Bryan, TX</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-09-01 10:00:07</Time>
        <Amount>$25.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
      <Bid>
        <Bidder Rating="15" UserID="allyw1">
          <Location>New York</Location>
          <Country>USA</Country>
        </Bidder>
        <Time>Dec-10-01 12:40:07</Time>
        <Amount>$28.00</Amount>
      </Bid>
    </Bids>
    <Location Latitude="38.638318" Longitude="-90.427118">Missouri The Show Me State</Location>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Started>Dec-03-01 20:40:07</Started>
    <Ends>Dec-13-01 20:40:07</Ends>
    <Seller Rating="813" UserID="lwm123" />
    <Description>Precious Moments Fig-ANGEL OF MERCY- NURSE Click picture to enlarge Makes a great gift for Collectors Description Up for bids is this great figurine from Precious Moments. It is #102482, ANGEL OF MERCY. It is a 5 1/2 inch figurine of an angel nurse. She is carrying a plant. It is really cute, just look at the pictures. It was released in 1986. This figurine bears the FIRST production mark of the Olive Branch. It is in EXCELLENT condition. It has only been displayed in a glass case and comes in its original box with all production tags included. The bidding starts at $9.99 with NO RESERVE!!! THANK YOU FOR LOOKING AND HAPPY BIDDING!!!!!!!!!!!!!! US Shipping is $5.60 for Priority Mail with tracking. International shipping, including Canada, is different depending on destination. International bidders, including Canada, must pay through Pay Pal or in US Cash. Email with any questions. Insurance, if desired, is extra. 0-$50.=1.10 - $51.-$100.=$2.00 -$101.-$200.=$3.00 - $201 - $250.=$4.00. Winning bidder must make contact within 3 days and payment must be received witin 10 days (21 days for international winners) or Ebay will be contacted and item relisted. If you don't intend to complete the transaction, Please Don't Bid. Details Click picture to enlarge Condition Excellent This item is in EXCELLENT condition it has only been displayed in a glass case. It comes in its original box with all production tags included!!!!! Payment and Shipping Info Payment Options Money Order/Cashier's Check or Personal Check _ _ _ Shipping Fixed Shipping Charges.$5.60 (Domestic) Will Ship Internationally Quantity Available 1 Special! PLEASE CLICK THE LINK BELOW TO VIEW MY OTHER ITEMS. It Shows ALL My Auctions!!!...I have many quality Precious Moments Figurines and Dolls up for bids with values up to $250.00....ALL with starting bids of $9.99 or less and ALL with NO RESERVE!!!...CHECK THEM OUT!!!!!.... Combine auctions and SAVE on shipping!!!...I accept Pay Pal, Money Orders and Personal Checks. Please note there is 10 day hold on shipping till Personal Checks clear. Click picture to enlarge _ Click picture to enlarge _ Click picture to enlarge _ Click picture to enlarge _ Click picture to enlarge _ Use the REAL selling tools a million sellers do - Andale!</Description>
  </Item>
